Guide to the Delta Gamma, Chi chapter records, 1874-2013
Delta Gamma, Chi chapter records,
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Delta Gamma, Chi chapter records,. 1874-2013
37-4-4071
Delta Gamma
5 cubic feet
Correspondence, financial documents, photographs, printed materials
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Records of the Chi chapter at Cornell of Delta Gamma.
ORGANIZATIONAL HISTORY
The Chi chapter was founded in 1885 at Cornell University.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Records of the Chi chapter at Cornell of Delta Gamma. Collection contains information regarding history, operations and activities including the Delta Gamma Property Association, Panhellenic items, the Anchora publication, philanthropy, financial items, and roster of members. Also information and photographs pertaining to various conventions and the 1985 centennial and 2010 anniversary celebrations. Includes the original charter given to the national for the Chi chapter.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Delta Gamma; Cornell University -- Societies, etc.; Cornell University -- Students.
Subjects:
Greek letter societies.; Women college students.; Women -- Societies, etc.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
SERIES LIST
Series I. Delta Gamma General Documents
Series II. Building and Construction Papers
Series III. Alumni and Memorabilia
Delta Gamma Chi Centennial and 125th
Series IV. The Anchora of Delta Gamma
Series V. Additional Publications
CONTAINER LIST
- Series I. Delta Gamma General Documents
  - Delta Gamma Fraternity Charter, March, 3, 1885 (Mapcase-folder 2)
    Given to Rachel Meyers, Lucy Alvord, Esther M. Sanford, Fredrika Meloy, and Kate Selmser. Signed by Emma Goddard, Emma Drinker, Regina Lindeman, and Belle Brown, Madison Wisconsin.
  - Chi History: Anchora, 1885-1935 (Not all submissions), 1885-1935 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Delta Gamma Miscellaneous Clippings and Letters, 1960s-1970s (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - University-Fraternity Relations, 1966-1970 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Delta Gamma: Fraternity and Foundation, Constitutions, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Bed and Breakfast, 1985-2003 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Delta Gamma Scholarships, 1985-2003 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - By-Laws and Standing Rules Chi Chapter of Delta Gamma, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Journal of Notes Relating to Delta Gamma (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - CHI Alumnae Newsletters, 1948-2005 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Newsletter, 1985-2001 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Delta Gamma Checkbooks, 1967-1990 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Delta Gamma Member Lists, 1969-2013 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - DG Newsletters, Ithaca Alumnae Chapter Copies, 1983-2009 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Delta Gamma Alumnae Chapter Stamp (Box 5)
- Series II. Building and Construction Papers
  - Correspondence on 117 Triphammer Road Building Addition, December 1964-August 1966 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Delta Gamma Floor Plans, 117 Triphammer Road, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Delta Gamma Alumni and Housing, 1983-1987 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Delta Gamma Cornell Heights, Historic Designation, 1987-1989 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Delta Gamma: House Corp. Files, 1987-2009 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Delta Gamma Property Assignments, 1989-1998 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Digital Images (Disks), Samples of Chapter House Line Drawing (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Delta Gamma 117 Triphammer Road, Condition Assessment Report, April 1998 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Series III. Alumni and Memorabilia
  - Delta Gamma Memorabilia, Gathered 2011, 2011 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Cornell Rush Books, 1983-1985 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Memorabilia from Laurra Ferres Fitts, '46 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    Includes Songs of Delta Gamma
  - Memorabilia from Janet Bassette Summerville, '46 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Memorabilia from Helen Tetter Kennedy, '47 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Memorabilia from Sharon Flynn, '57 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Memorabilia from Sally Johnson Steele, '59 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    Includes pledge manual.
  - Assorted Delta Gamma Portraits, ca. 1930s (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Delta Gamma Alumnae Tea at Agda Osborn Home, February 1996, February 1996 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - DGs 1980s, ca. 1990 (Mapcase-folder 1, Folder 1)
    Two collages of photographs of various DG individuals and activities throughout the 1980s.
  - Delta Gamma Centennial and 125th
    - Delta Gamma Chi Chapter Alumnae Philanthropy, 1984-2011, 1984-2011 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Delta Gamma Chi Chapter, Ithaca Alumnae, 1995-1999, 1995-1999 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Papers, Mainly Correspondence, Concerning Delta Gamma Chi's Centennial, 1983-1984, 1983-1984 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Delta Gamma Chi Papers, Mainly Relating to Alumni, 1983-1985 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - CHI Alumnae: Informational Survey Responses alumnae through classes of the 1940s, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - CHI Alumnae: Informational Survey Responses alumnae from classes of the 1950s - 1960s, 1984-1985 (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - CHI Alumnae: Informational Survey Responses alumnae from classes of the 1970s - 1980s, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - Anchora Celebrates 100 Years of Excellence, Spring 1984 (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - Programs from Delta Gamma Chi Centennial, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - Packet from Delta Gamma Chi Centennial, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - Delta Gamma Chi: Centennial Celebration items from a binder, April 1985 (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - Delta Gamma Chi: Centennial Celebration items from a scrapbook, April 1985 (Box 1, Folder 40)
      Includes planning information and photographs.
    - Delta Gamma Chi Chapter, 125th Anniversary/Celebration, April 2010 (Box 1, Folder 41)
    - Delta Gamma Chi Chapter, 125th Anniversary Alumnae Questionnaires, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 42)
      Completed by Hand (Balance of Questionnaires Completed Online)
    - Delta Gamma Chi: Centennial Planning, 1985 (Box 3)
    - Delta Gamma Chi's Centennial T-Shirt, 1985 (Box 5)
- Series IV. The Anchora of Delta Gamma
  Not a complete run, there are missing bound and loose issues.
  - Volumes I - V, November 1884 - June 1889 (Box 2)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume I, Number 2, November 1884 (Box 2)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume I, Number 3, January 1885 (Box 2)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume I, Number 4, March 1885 (Box 2)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume II, Number 1, April 1885 (Box 2)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume II, Number 2, June 1885 (Box 2)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume III, Numbers 1, 2, April, June 1886 (Box 2)
      Single issue containing two volumes.
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume III, Number 3, November 1886 (Box 2)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume III, Number 4, March 1887 (Box 2)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume III, Number 5, June 1887 (Box 2)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume IV, Number 1, November 1887 (Box 2)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume IV, Number 2, February 1888 (Box 2)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume IV, Number 3, April 1888 (Box 2)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume IV, Number 4, June 1888 (Box 2)
      Loose issue, not bound within this set.
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume V, Number 2, February 1889 (Box 2)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume V, Number 3, April 1889 (Box 2)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume V, Number 4, June 1889 (Box 2)
  - Volumes IX - XI, November 1892 - June 1895 (Box 2)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume IX, Number 1, November 1892 (Box 2)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume IX, Number 2, January 1893 (Box 2)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume IX, Number 3, April 1893 (Box 2)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume IX, Number 4, June 1893 (Box 2)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume X, Number 2, January 1894 (Box 2)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume X, Number 3, April 1894 (Box 2)
      Bound out of order before previous issue.
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume X, Number 4, June 1894 (Box 2)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume XI, Number 1, November 1894 (Box 2)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume XI, Number 2, January 1895 (Box 2)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume XI, Number 3, April 1895 (Box 2)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume XI, Number 4, June 1895 (Box 2)
  - Volumes XII - XIV, November 1895 - June 1898 (Box 2)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume XII, Number 1, November 1895 (Box 2)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume XII, Number 2, January 1896 (Box 2)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume XII, Number 3, April 1896 (Box 2)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume XII, Number 4, June 1896 (Box 2)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume XIII, Number 1, November 1896 (Box 2)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume XIII, Number 2, January 1897 (Box 2)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume XIV, Number 1, November 1897 (Box 2)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume XIV, Number 2, January 1898 (Box 2)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume XIV, Number 3, April 1898 (Box 2)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume XIV, Number 4, June 1898 (Box 2)
  - Volumes XV - XVII, November 1898 - July 1901 (Box 2)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume XV, Number 1, November 1898 (Box 2)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume XV, Number 3, April 1899 (Box 2)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume XV, Number 4, July 1899 (Box 2)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume XVI, Number 1, November 1899 (Box 2)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume XVI, Number 2, January 1900 (Box 2)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume XVI, Number 3, April 1900 (Box 2)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume XVI, Number 4, June 1900 (Box 2)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume XVII, Number 1, November 1900 (Box 2)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume XVII, Number 2, January 1901 (Box 2)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume XVII, Number 3, April 1901 (Box 2)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume XVII, Number 4, July 1901 (Box 2)
  - Volumes XVIII - XX, November 1901 - July 1904 (Box 2)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume XVIII, Number 1, November 1901 (Box 2)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume XVIII, Number 2, January 1902 (Box 2)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume XVIII, Number 3, April 1902 (Box 2)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume XVIII, Number 4, July 1902 (Box 2)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume IXX, Number 1, November 1902 (Box 2)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume IXX, Number 3, April 1903 (Box 2)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume IXX, Number 4, July 1903 (Box 2)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume XX, Number 1, November 1903 (Box 2)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume XX, Number 2, January 1904 (Box 2)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume XX, Number 3, April 1904 (Box 2)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume XX, Number 4, July 1904 (Box 2)
  - Volumes XXI - XXIV, November 1904 - April 1907 (Box 2)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume XXI, Number 1, November 1904 (Box 2)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume XXI, Number 2, January 1905 (Box 2)
      Incorrectly published as Volume XXII.
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume XXI, Number 3, April 1905 (Box 2)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume XXII, Number 2, January 1906 (Box 2)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume XXII, Number 3, April 1906 (Box 2)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume XXII, Number 4, July 1906 (Box 2)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume XXIII, Number 1, November 1906 (Box 2)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume XXIII, Number 2, January 1907 (Box 2)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume XXIII, Number 3, April 1907 (Box 2)
      Incorrectly published as Volume XXIV.
  - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume XXVI, Number 1, November 1909 (Box 2)
    Loose issue.
  - Issues from 1911, January 1911 - November 1911 (Box 2)
    The first issue in the volume is bound out of order.
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume XXVII, Number 2, January 1911 (Box 2)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume XXVII, Number 3, April 1911 (Box 2)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume XXVII, Number 4, July 1911 (Box 2)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume XXVIII, Number 1, November 1911 (Box 2)
      Bound out of order at front of volume
  - Issues from 1913, January 1913 - November 1913 (Box 2)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume XXIX, Number 2, January 1913 (Box 2)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume XXIX, Number 3, April 1913 (Box 2)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume XXIX, Number 4, June 1913 (Box 2)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume XXX, Number 1, November 1913 (Box 2)
  - Issues from 1914, January 1914 - November 1914 (Box 2)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume XXX, Number 2, January 1914 (Box 2)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume XXX, Number 3, April 1914 (Box 2)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume XXX, Number 4, June 1914 (Box 2)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume XXXI, Number 1, November 1914 (Box 2)
  - Issues from 1916, January 1916 - November 1916 (Box 2)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume XXXII, Number 2, January 1916 (Box 2)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume XXXII, Number 3, April 1916 (Box 2)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume XXXII, Number 4, June 1916 (Box 2)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume XXXIII, Number 1, November 1916 (Box 2)
  - Issues from 1917, January 1917 - November 1917 (Box 2)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume XXXIII, Number 2, January 1917 (Box 2)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume XXXIII, Number 3, April 1917 (Box 2)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume XXXIII, Number 4, June 1917 (Box 2)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume XXXIV, Number 1, November 1917 (Box 2)
      Bound out of order at front of volume.
  - Issues from 1918, January 1918 - November 1918 (Box 2)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume XXXIV, Number 2, January 1918 (Box 2)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume XXXIV, Number 3, April 1918 (Box 2)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume XXXIV, Number 4, June 1918 (Box 2)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume XXXV, Number 1, November 1918 (Box 2)
  - Issues from 1919, January 1919 - November 1919 (Box 2)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume XXXV, Number 2, January 1919 (Box 2)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume XXXV, Number 3, April 1919 (Box 2)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume XXXVI, Number 1, November 1919 (Box 2)
  - Loose Issues, January 1920 - May 1935
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume XXXVI Number 2, January 1920 (Box 2)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma,Volume XXXVI Number 3, April 1920 (Box 2)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume XXXVI Number 4, June 1920 (Box 2)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume XXXVII Number 1, November 1920 (Box 2)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume XXXVII Number 3, April 1921 (Box 2)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume XXXVII Number 4, June 1921 (Box 2)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume XXXVIII Number 1, November 1921 (Box 3)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume XXXVIII Number 2, January 1922 (Box 3)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume XXXVIII Number 3, March 1922 (Box 3)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume XXXVIII Number 4, May 1922 (Box 3)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma,Volume XXXIX Number 2, January 1923 (Box 3)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume XXXIX Number 3, March 1923 (Box 3)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume XXXIX Number 4r, May 1923 (Box 3)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume XXXX Number 1, November 1923 (Box 3)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume XXXX Number 2, January 1924 (Box 3)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume XXXX Number 3, March 1924 (Box 3)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume XXXX Number 4, May 1924 (Box 3)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume XLI Number 1, November 1924 (Box 3)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume XLI Number 2, January 1925 (Box 3)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume XLI Number 3, March 1925 (Box 3)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume XLI Number 4, May 1925 (Box 3)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume XLII Number 1, November 1925 (Box 3)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume XLII Number 2, January 1926 (Box 3)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume XLII Number 3, March 1926 (Box 3)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume XLII Number 4, May 1926 (Box 3)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume XLIII Number 1, November 1926 (Box 3)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume XLIII Number 2, January 1927 (Box 3)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume XLIII Number 3, March 1927 (Box 3)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume XLIV Number 1, November 1927 (Box 3)
      Published with no issue number given.
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume XLIV Number 2, January 1928 (Box 3)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume XLIV Number 4, May 1928 (Box 3)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume XLV Number 1, November 1928 (Box 3)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume XLV Number 2, January 1929 (Box 3)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume XLV Number 3, March 1929 (Box 3)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume XLV Number 4, May 1929 (Box 3)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume XLVI Number 1, November 1929 (Box 3)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume XLVI Number 2, January 1930 (Box 3)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume XLVI Number 3, March 1930 (Box 3)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume XLVII Number 4, Part 1, May 1931 (Box 3)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume XLVIII Number 1, November 1931 (Box 3)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume XLVIII Number 3, Part 1, March 1932 (Box 3)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume XLIX Number 1, November 1932 (Box 3)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume XLIX Number 2, January 1933 (Box 3)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume XLIX Number 3, March 1933 (Box 3)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume XLIX Number 4, May 1933 (Box 3)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume L Number 1, November 1933 (Box 3)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume L Number 2, January 1934 (Box 3)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume L Number 3, March 1934 (Box 3)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume L Number 4, May 1934 (Box 3)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume LI Number 1, November 1934 (Box 3)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume LI Number 4, May 1935 (Box 3)
  - Volume LII, November 1935 - May 1936 (Box 3)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume LII, Number 1, November 1935 (Box 3)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume LII, Number 2, January 1936 (Box 3)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume LII, Number 3, March 1936 (Box 3)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume LII, Number 4, May 1936 (Box 3)
  - Volume LIII, November 1936 - May 1937 (Box 3)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume LIII, Number 1, November 1936 (Box 3)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume LIII, Number 2, January 1937 (Box 3)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume LIII, Number 3, March 1937 (Box 3)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume LIII, Number 4, May 1937 (Box 3)
  - Volume LIV, November 1937 - May 1938 (Box 3)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume LIV, Number 1, November 1937 (Box 3)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume LIV, Number 2, January 1938 (Box 3)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume LIV, Number 3, March 1938 (Box 3)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume LIV, Number 4, May 1938 (Box 3)
  - Volume LV, November 1938 - May 1939 (Box 3)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume LV, Number 1, November 1938 (Box 3)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume LV, Number 2, January 1939 (Box 3)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume LV, Number 3, March 1939 (Box 3)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume LV, Number 4, May 1939 (Box 3)
  - Volume LVI, November 1939 - May 1940 (Box 3)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume LVI, Number 1, November 1939 (Box 3)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume LVI, Number 2, January 1940 (Box 3)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume LVI, Number 3, March 1940 (Box 3)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume LVI, Number 4, May 1940 (Box 3)
  - Volume LVII, November 1940 - May 1941 (Box 3)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume LVII, Number 1, November 1940 (Box 3)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume LVII, Number 2, January 1941 (Box 3)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume LVII, Number 3, March 1941 (Box 3)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume LVII, Number 4, May 1941 (Box 3)
  - Volume LIX, November 1942 - May 1943 (Box 3)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume LIX, Number 1, November 1942 (Box 3)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume LIX, Number 2, January 1943 (Box 3)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume LIX, Number 3, March 1943 (Box 3)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume LIX, Number 4, May 1943 (Box 3)
  - Volume LX, November 1943 - May 1944 (Box 3)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume LX, Number 1, November 1943 (Box 3)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume LX, Number 2, January 1944 (Box 3)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume LX, Number 3, March 1944 (Box 3)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume LX, Number 4, May 1944 (Box 3)
  - Volume LXII, November 1945 - May 1946 (Box 3)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume LXII, Number 1, November 1945 (Box 3)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume LXII, Number 2, January 1946 (Box 3)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume LXII, Number 3, March 1946 (Box 3)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume LXII, Number 4, May 1946 (Box 3)
  - Volume LXIII, November 1946 - May 1947 (Box 3)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume LXIII, Number 1, November 1946 (Box 3)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume LXIII, Number 2, January 1947 (Box 3)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume LXIII, Number 3, March 1947 (Box 3)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume LXIII, Number 4, May 1947 (Box 3)
  - Volume LXIV, November 1947 - May 1948 (Box 4)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume LXIV, Number 1, November 1947 (Box 4)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume LXIV, Number 2, January 1948 (Box 4)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume LXIV, Number 3, March 1948 (Box 4)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume LXIV, Number 4, May 1948 (Box 4)
  - Volume LXV, November 1948 - May 1949 (Box 4)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume LXV, Number 1, November 1948 (Box 4)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume LXV, Number 2, January 1949 (Box 4)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume LXV, Number 3, March 1949 (Box 4)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume LXV, Number 4, May 1949 (Box 4)
  - Volume LXVI, November 1949 - May 1950 (Box 4)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume LXVI, Number 1, November 1949 (Box 4)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume LXVI, Number 2, January 1950 (Box 4)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume LXVI, Number 3, March 1950 (Box 4)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume LXVI, Number 4, May 1950 (Box 4)
  - Volume LXVII, November 1950 - May 1951 (Box 4)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume LXVII, Number 1, November 1950 (Box 4)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume LXVII, Number 2, January 1951 (Box 4)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume LXVII, Number 3, March 1951 (Box 4)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume LXVII, Number 4, May 1951 (Box 4)
  - Volume LXVIII, November 1951 - May 1952 (Box 4)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume LXVIII, Number 1, November 1951 (Box 4)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume LXVIII, Number 2, January 1952 (Box 4)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume LXVIII, Number 3, March 1952 (Box 4)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume LXVIII, Number 4, May 1952 (Box 4)
  - Volume LXIX, November 1952 - Summer 1953 (Box 4)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume LXIX, Number 1, November 1952 (Box 4)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume LXIX, Number 2, January 1953 (Box 4)